"反应炉3分钟后就要爆炸
"We've got three minutes till the reactor blows.
我们逃不掉了"
We'll never make it!"
"你得赶快逃命 救你自己"
"You've got to get out of here! Save yourself!"
"不行 我不会扔下你"
"No, I won't leave you."
"别管我 我是机器人 我只是一台机器"
"Don't worry about me. I'm a robot. I'm just a machine!"
- "不 对我来说不是"   - 天哪
- "No, you're not. Not to me."     - Oh, my God.
- 怎样？ - 我太有才华了
- What?     - I am extremely talented.
- 你确很棒   - 是啊
- Yeah. You're great.     - Yeah.
- 好 我们从...   - 不是 我真的超会演的
- Okay, let's take it from...     - No, I was really acting my ass off.
我觉得我也很不错
I thought I was pretty good too.
你是很不错 只不过不是我
Yeah, you're solid. You're just no me.
我看就先这样
You know what? I think that's enough for now.
我不想排练过头
I don't want to be over-rehearsed. Ha-ha-ha.
没关系 我自己演
Fine. I'll do it without you!
我不需要你或任何人
I don't need you or anybody else!
我会靠我自己成功
I'm gonna make it on my own!
等着瞧 都给我等着瞧
You'll see! You'll all see!
老友记 第六季 第二十集
你要去试什么镜？
So, what's this thing you're auditioning for?
是一部新影集
It's a new TV show. Yeah.
我的角色叫麦克麦可维利 也叫麦克
I'm up for the part of Mac, Machiavelli, or "Mac"!
我是个侦探 和我的机器人拍档 一起打击犯罪
I'm a detective and I solve crimes with the help of my robot partner.
他是人性化电脑
He's a computerized, humanoid...
电子秘密杀手
electronically enhanced secret enforcer.
简称吉事
Or, "C.H.E.E.S.E."
- 所以是麦克与吉事   - 那就是剧名
- So, Mac and C.H.E.E.S. E?     - That's the title!
幸好缩写刚好是吉事
They really lucked out that the initials spell "cheese."
真是幸好
That is lucky.
要是你拿到这个角色
Huh. So, Joey, if you get this, you're gonna be, like...
就有你自己的影集了
the star of your own TV show.
你就会被称为大吉事(汉堡) 或是大麦克(麦香堡) 都是你的最爱
I mean, you'll be like the "Big Cheese" or the "Big Mac." Hey, you love those!
别抱太大期望 可能没那么好
Don't get your hopes up, because it's probably not gonna happen.
你为什么要这么说？
Now, why would you say that, Joseph?
拜托 我主演的影集耶？
Well, I mean, come on, you guys. My own TV show?
- 我都不知道我配不配   - 我配
- I don't know if I'm good enough.     - I am. Heh.
乔伊 你在说什么？你是个很棒的演员
What are you talking about? You're a terrific actor.
- 真的吗？ - 你怎么能这么问
- You really think so?     - How can you even ask that question?
- 她真漂亮   - 对 人也很好
- She's pretty.     - Yeah. And she's really nice too.
她教我怎么面对镜头
She taught me all about, you know, how to work with cameras...
和闻屁演技法
and "smell the fart" acting.
- 什么？ - 什么？
- I'm sorry, what'd you say?     - Excuse me?
因为在短时问内要背很多台词
It's like you got so many lines to learn so fast...
有时得停下来想下一句
that sometimes you need a minute to remember your next one.
在你想的时候 要来个大停顿 表情故作严肃
So while you're thinking of it, you take this big pause where you look all intense.
就像这样
You know, like this:
- 噢   - 好
- Oh.     - Okay.
该我了该我了
Here's my scene! Here's my scene!
华勒斯太太 我是雷莫瑞医生 令妹的神经外科医生
Mrs. Wallace? I'm Dr. Drake Ramoray, your sister's neurosurgeon.
令妹得了一种...
You sister is suffering from a...
伊娃 我们有不错的进展
Well, Eva, we've done some excellent work here.
老实说 你的困扰很清楚
And I would have to say, your problem is quite clear.
# All you want is a dinkle #
# What you envy's a schwang #
# A thing through which you can tinkle #
# Or play with or simply let hang #
我演艾尔帕西诺的屁股
I play Al Pacino's butt.
好吗？他进去淋浴 然后我就是他的屁股
All right? He goes into the shower and then, I'm his butt.
- 天哪   - 别这样
- Oh, my God.     - Come on, you guys.
这是一部 艾尔帕西诺主演的电影 很不得了
This is a real movie and Al Pacino's in it, and that's big!
的确很棒 你当之无愧 努力了这么久
No, it's terrific. You deserve this after all your years of struggling...
终于可以"屁美"别人了
you've finally been able to crack your way into show business.
好 你们笑吧 我不在乎 这是我的一大突破
Okay, fine, make jokes. I don't care. This is a big break for me.
- 你说得很对   - 是啊
- No, you're right, it is.     - Yeah.
你会找我们去看你"精屁"的演出吗？
So, you gonna invite us all to the big opening?
好 我要走了 祝我好运
All right, I'm out of here. Wish me luck.
加油 加油 我们祝你好运
Good luck, good luck We all wish you good luck
随便啦
Yeah, whatever.
该你了
It's your turn.
我们有在玩喔？
Oh, are we playing this?
- 嗨   - 嗨 试镜结果如何？
- Hey.     - Hey. How did the audition go?
很烂 我把台词都念错了 我不该当演员的
Terrible. I messed up every line. I shouldn't even be an actor.
等等 你又在假装不顺利了
Wait. Are you doing that thing where you pretend it didn't go well...
其实很顺利？
but it really did go well?
- 对 有唬过你们吗？ - 一愣一愣的
- Yeah, did I fool you?     - Totally!
- 所以很顺利罗   - 顺利的不得了
- So, it did go well?     - It went amazingly well!
- 太好了   - 太好了
- Great.     - That's great.
- 只剩我和另外两个人三选   - 天哪
- It's down to me and two other guys.     - Oh, my God.
那两个人都很厉害
I know both of them, and they're really good.
其中一个就是在过敏广告里
One's from those allergy commercials who's always being chased...
- 被巨无霸花朵追来追去的人   - 我好喜欢那个人
- by those big flowers.     - Oh, I love that guy.
你在干什么？
Oh. What are you doing?
我在干什么？
What am I doing?
我好紧张 明天下午5点才要复试
I'm so nervous, you know? The callback isn't till tomorrow at 5.
我的头好像要爆炸了
I feel like my head's gonna explode.
你的头早该爆了
Well, it is overdue.
放心 你一定没问题
Don't worry, okay? You're gonna be fine.
压力真的好大
Yeah, but it's so much pressure.
很抱歉 但你们的工作很不同
No offense, but what you guys all do is very different.
我不知道你们能不能体会
I don't know if you'd understand.
是啊 我们的工作都没有压力
Yeah, none of the rest of us have to deal with pressure at our jobs.
我知道现在几点了
Yes, I know what time it is...
但是我对这份报告很不满意
but I'm looking at the WENIS and I'm not happy.
我在撕生菜
Well, I'm tearing the lettuce.
- 它脏吗？ - 放心 我会洗
- Uh-huh? Is it dirty?     - No, don't worry, I'm gonna wash it.
不必 我喜欢脏脏的
Don't. I like it dirty.
你决定就好
That's your call.
你接下来要做什么？
So, uh, what are you going to do next?
我要切蕃茄
Well, I thought that I would cut up the tomatoes.
它们结实吗？
Are they firm?
还不差
They're all right.
你确定它们没有变坏？你确定它们没有很坏很坏？
You sure they haven't gone bad? You sure they're not very, very bad?
它们还好
No, really. They're okay.
你会把它们切得很漂亮吗？
You gonna slice them up real nice?
其实我想用手捏
Ahem. Actually, I was gonna do them julienne.
我要走了
I'm out of here.
摩妮卡 我要辞职 我帮一个老女人挤进丁字裤
Monica, I'm quitting. I just helped an 81-year-old woman put on a thong...
结果她根本没买
and she didn't even buy it.
我要辞职 我现在就要跟老板说
I'm quitting. That's it. I'm talking to my boss right now.
我要 我要...
Yes, I am. Yes, I am.
再见 听到留言请回电
Okay, bye. Call me when you get this message.
怎么了？
Well, what happened?
他来按摩 本来都没事 后来...
Well, he came in for a massage, and everything was fine until...
天哪
Oh, my God.
然后突然间毛手毛脚成了小事
And all of a sudden, his hands weren't the problem anymore.
- 他有没有...   - 用来搭帐棚都绰绰有余
- Was it?     - Oh, Boy Scouts could've camped under there.
你吃了我的三明治？
You ate my sandwich.
很单纯的错误 谁都可能会犯
It was a simple mistake. It could happen to anyone.
是吗？
Oh, really?
你别激动
Now calm down.
来我的办公室找 垃圾桶里可能还有
Come look in my office. Some of it may still be in the trash.
- 什么？ - 它很大
- What?     - Well, it was quite large.
我只好扔掉大半
I had to throw most of it away.
你...你扔掉我的三明治
You threw my sandwich away?
我的三明治？
My sandwich?
我的三明治
My sandwich!
我好想拿到这个角色
It's just, I want this part so much, you know?
要是我没拿到 我就再也不吃起司通心面
If I don't get this part, I'm never gonna eat macaroni and cheese again.
不 我没说 我骗人
No, I didn't say that. That doesn't count.
别这样 我又不是搬去欧洲
Come on, guys. It's not like I moved to Europe.
我只是搬到对面
I just moved across the hall.
我们也想经常请你们来坐
And we would have you over all the time...
但是摩妮卡会过敏
if it weren't for Monica's allergies.
没错 我骗不了你们
You're right, I could never lie to you.
她讨厌你们
She hates you.
要接吗？
Should I get that? Ha-ha-ha.
喂？乔伊现在不在
Hello? Uh, no, Joey's not here right now.
你要留官吗？
Can I take a message?
好 试镜从5点改到2点半？
Yeah, okay. So the audition's been moved from 5 to 2:30?
好的 再见
Okay, great. Bye.
- 你还没穿衣服？ - 我又光着身体了？
- Aren't you dressed yet?     - Am I naked again?
我们15分钟后要去见我爸妈
We're supposed to meet my parents in 15 minutes.
好 我只是在跟他们聊天
Okay. I was just talking to the guys. Just look at them.
你看他们嘛 他们可以去找我们吗？
I mean, is it okay if they come visit?
那我的过敏怎么办？
What about my allergies?
也对 你会过敏
Right. Your allergies.
都是她 她讨厌你们
All her. She hates you.
喔 喔 喔
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
漂亮
Yes! All right.
要是这些小人能变成真人大小 该有多酷？
How cool would it be if you could watch like a real life-size version of this?
- 该有多过瘾？ - 跟足球一样过瘾？
- I mean, how crazy would that be?     - As crazy as soccer?
喂？
Hello?
你在说什么？5点才试镜
What are you talking about? The audition's not till 5.
没有人告诉我
Well, nobody told me.
你跟谁说的？
Who'd you talk to?
没事
Never mind.
这样你看不懂吗？
You mean you didn't get it from this?
那个过敏人入选了 谢谢你啊
The allergy guy got the part. Thanks.
也许还可以补救
Maybe we can fix it, you know?
我们可以送巨无霸花去吓他
Maybe we can send him some big, big flowers and scare him!
你怎么能这样？
How could you do this to me?
钱德 这个角色可以让我的事业翻红
This part could've turned my whole career around.
是我的错 对不起 我真的搞砸了
I messed up, okay? I'm sorry. I really messed up.
你根本也不住这里了 干嘛接我的电话？
You don't even live here anymore. Why'd you answer my phone?
- 我有答录机   - 是我买给你的
- I have a machine!     - Which I bought for you.
还教你怎么使用 你以为它是影印机
Taught you how to use it. You thought it was a copier.
我愿意尽全力挽救这个错误
If there was anything I could do, I would do it, okay?
但是人起码可以犯一次错
But everybody's allowed one mistake, right?
他可以送我录影机 可以送我高尔夫球具
He could have gotten me a VCR. He could have gotten me golf clubs.
可是他偏偏要让我把女人吓跑
But no, he has to get me the "woman repeller."
一个废五金行里最丑的东西
The eyesore from the "Liberace House of Crap!"
- 没那么严重啦   - 说得轻巧
- It's not that bad.     - Easy for you to say.
你又不必戴着 被某个老粗淘汰的金饰到处跑
You don't have to sport a reject from the "Mr. T Collection."
钱德 钱德
Chandler. Chandler.
我真同情戴这个手饰的人 真的
I pity the fool who puts on my jewelry! I do! I do!
我真同情戴这个...
I pity the fool that...
你好
Hi...
你昨天晚归 凯西和我聊了起来
When you were late last night, Kathy and I got to talking...
事情演变到后来就...
and one thing led to another and...
就什么？你跟她上床？
And what? Did you sleep with her?
- 没有 我只是吻了她   - 什么？那样更糟
- No! No, I just kissed her.     - What? That's even worse!
- 怎么会更糟？ - 我不知道 反正都一样
- How is that worse?     - I don't know! But it's the same!
你说得对 我无话可说 我太过分了
You're right, I have no excuses. I was totally over the line.
过分？
"Over the line?"
你根本就过分到连过分见到你
You're so far past the line that you can't even see the line!
都会说你过分
Yeah, the line is a dot to you!
我不是要你奇迹式的原谅我
I'm not saying that you should magically forgive me.
但你也不完美 你也做过错误的判断
But you're not perfect. You've made some errors in judgment too.
举个例子
Name one.
怎么回事？
What happened?
他答应不拿沙发椅的
Aw, man! He promised he wouldn't take the chairs!
怎么回事？你怎么会被关进去
What the hell happened? How were you locked in?
我们的东西呢？
And where the hell's all of our stuff?
有一个人来看柜子
This guy came by to look at the unit...
他说它塞不下一个大人
and he said he didn't think it was big enough to fit a grown man.
所以你就自愿进去？
So you got in voluntarily?
我想把柜子卖出去
I was trying to make a sale!
要是让我碰上他 你猜我会怎样？
Oh, man, if I ever run into that guy again, you know what I'm gonna do?
把屁股翘起来？
Bend over?
她来了
There's Lorraine.
记住 不准交换 美女是你的 失恋女是我的
Okay, now remember, no trading. You get the pretty one, I get the mess.
- 嗨 乔伊   - 嘿
- Hi, Joey.     - Hey.
他就是你带来的人
Well, well. Look what you brought.
你又带了谁来？
And what did you bring?
她在寄放外套
She's checking her coat.
乔伊 我要去洗个手
Joey, I'm gonna go wash the cab smell off my hands.
你帮我叫一杯白酒 帮珍妮丝叫一杯红酒
Will you get me a white Zinfandel and a glass of red for Janice?
珍妮丝？
Janice?
我的天哪
Oh, my God!
乔伊的栽缝吃我豆腐
Joey's tailor took advantage of me.
什么？
What?
不可能 我找他做了12年衣服
No way. I've been going to the guy for 12 years.
拜托啦 他说要量裤管内侧
He said he was gonna do my inseam...
然后他的手一路模上来 然后就...
then he ran his hand up my leg and then there was definite...
怎样？
What?
包住了
Cupping.
裤子就是那样量的
That's how they do pants!
罗斯 你告诉他
Ross, will you tell him?
- 裤子不都是那样量的？ - 是啊是啊...在监狱里
- Isn't that how a tailor measures pants?     - Yes, yes, it is. In prison!
叫你举一个就好
I said name one!
- 我居然这么粗心 我真白痴   - 别再自责了
- I can't believe I did this. What an idiot.     - Stop beating yourself up.
人都会犯错 这是难免的
People make mistakes. These things happen.
你没有忘记帮我记留言吧？
There aren't any messages you've forgotten to give me, are there?
显然你不太会记留言
Apparently, you're not very good at it.
- 你们觉得他会原谅我吗？ - 当然会
- Do you think he'll ever forgive me?     - Of course he will.
但最重要的是 你得原谅自己
Chandler, the most important thing is that you forgive yourself.
- 其实我已经原谅自己了   - 这么快？
- You know what, I kind of have.     - Already?
你犯的错蛮严重的
That was pretty bad, what you did.
他会原谅你的
You know what? He will forgive you.
我接电话时都会带便条纸... 好啦
I like to bring a pad with me when I go answer the phone, just in case. Okay.
你没看到他气成什么样子
You didn't see how mad he was, you know?
他一定会原谅你的
I'm sure he will forgive you.
我们都有这种经验 吵架 和解
Look, we've all been there, you know? You fight, you make up.
就是这样
That's the way it works.
这段感情会破裂是两个人的错
It took two people to break up this relationship!
对 你和影印店那个女的
Yeah! You and that girl from the copy place...
你昨天表明愿意负责
which yesterday you took full responsibility for!
我不知道我负的是什么责
I didn't know what I was taking responsibility for, okay?
我没把信看完
I didn't finish the whole letter.
- 什么？ - 我睡着了
- What?     - I fell asleep.
你睡着了？
You fell asleep?
当时是早上5点半
It was 5:30 in the morning.
你一废话就废话了十八页
And you had rambled on for 18 pages.
正反面都写满了
Front and back!
还有"你得"是指"你必须"
And by the way? Y-O-U, apostrophe R-E means, "you are."
"你的"是所有格
Y-O-U-R means "your."
我居然会想跟你复合
I can't believe I thought of getting back together with you.
我们根本就完了
We are so over!
无所谓
Fine by me!
顺便告诉你 那种事并不常见
And just so you know, it's not that common...
并非男人都会那样 那是很严重的
it doesn't happen to every guy, and it is a big deal!
我就知道
I knew it!
- 你没有权利和他约会   - 这真是太荒谬...
- You had no right to go out with him.     - That is the most ridiculous...
- 你出卖我   - 我没有出卖你
- You sold me out!     - I did not sell you out!
- 你出卖了   - 让我说话好吗？
- Yes, you did! You absolutely sold me...     - Would you let me talk?
你弹我的额头吗？
Did you just flick me?
你不让我说完 我很...
Okay, well, you wouldn't let me finish and I was just... Ow!
- 住手 噢   - 噢
- Stop it! Ow!     - Ow!
- 住手   - 住手
- Stop.     - Stop.
- 好 不要这样   - 不
- All right. No, let's not do this.     - No!
- 想想快乐的事   - 不
- Happy thoughts.     - No!
- 住手   - 噢 噢
- Stop it!     - Oh! Oh!
好 我要发威了
Okay, now I'm gonna kick some ass!
- 噢   - 噢
- Ow!     - Ow!
- 噢 噢 噢   - 我明白了
- Ow. Ow. Ow.     - I know, I know.
好 你们住手 我就放手
All right. Now, I will let go if you both stop.
- 好吧   - 好吧
- Fine.     - Fine.
这不就结了
There we go.
如果我们在监狱 你们就是我的喽罗
Ha. You know what? If we were in prison, you guys would be like my bitches.
兄弟 如何啊
Okay, buddy boy, here it is.
你藏我的衣服 我就穿你全部的衣服
You hide my clothes? I'm wearing everything you own.
我的天哪
Oh, my God!
看啊 我是钱德 我穿的衣服够多吧？
Look at me, I'm Chandler! Could I be wearing any more clothes?
因为我去玩野战游戏
Maybe if I wasn't going "commando."
穿这么多衣服真热 我最好别做弓箭步
Whew. I tell you, it's hot with all this stuff on. I'd better not do any lunges.
乔伊？
Joey?
我买了欢乐套餐 有两个披萨
Got you the Joey special. Two pizzas!
乔伊？
Joe?
喂？又来了
Hello? Damn it!
喂？
Hello?
乔伊现在不在 我可以帮你留官...应该吧
No, Joey's not here right now, but I can take a message. I think.
他还有机会？真是太好了
He's still got a chance for the part? That's great news!
我不是说那位被狗咬伤的演员
Well, no, obviously not for the actor who was mauled by his dog.
太好了 我会转告乔伊 谢谢
Well, that's great. I will give Joey the message. Thank you.
漂亮
Yes!
好
Okay.
麦克...
Mac...
试镜...
audition...
2点钟
at 2.
过敏...
Allergy...
演员...
actor...
遭攻击
attacked.
被狗...
By dog...
不是...
not...
被花
flowers.
- 嗨   - 请告诉我你有收到留言
- Hey.     - Please tell me you got the message.
- 什么留言？ - 要演麦克的演员不能演
- What message?     - The actor playing Mac couldn't do it.
- 他们要你2点过去   - 什么？明明是6点
- They needed to see you at 2:00.     - What? It's 6:00!
我有写在留言板上
Look! I wrote it! I wrote it on the board!
我写在留言板上 然后跑遍整个纽约找你
I wrote it on the board, then went looking all over for you!
我跑去罗斯家 跑去咖啡厅
I went to Ross's, the coffee house.
跑去每一个有三明治的地方
I went to any place that they make sandwiches!
- 我不敢相信 钱德   - 对不起
- I can't believe this, Chandler!     - I'm sorry.
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say!
那就说恭喜吧
You might say, "Congratulations."
我看到留官板 跑去试镜 我得到那角色了
I saw the board, I went to the audition, I got the part!
你觉得很好笑吗？我刚才真的很担心
Was that supposed to be funny? I was worried over here.
- 对不起   - 有时候这样骗人真的很恶劣
- I'm sorry.     - At times that fake-out thing is mean.
抱歉 我不是故意要害你内疚
Okay, man. I'm sorry. I did not mean to make you feel bad.
那就好
Well, that's good.
因为我没有内疚 我好替你高兴
Because you didn't. And I'm incredibly happy for you!
你好恶劣
That's mean!
- 你害我惭愧   - 再玩就玩不完了
- You had me going there!     - We could do this all day.
也对
Yeah, you're right.
好 我们来聊聊我会有多红
Look, let's talk about what a huge star I'm gonna be.
你会变成超级大明星
You are gonna be a huge star. I'm gonna hug you.
- 我要抱你   - 来抱吧
- You hug me.     - All right.
- 我们会不会太爱抱了？ - 我也觉得
- Do we do this too much?     - I think so.
- 放开我   - 就是啊
- Yeah. Get off me.     - Yeah.
"吉事 我不会扔下你的
"Come on, C.H.E.E.S.E., I'm not leaving without you.
你从中央处理器 启动备用电源"
Try routing your backup power source through your primary CPU."
"没办法 我的电路烧焦了 焦到不能再焦"
"I can't! My circuits are fried! They're fried, I tell you!"
哇哦
Wow.
"那我就背你"
"Well, then I'll just have to carry you."
"好棒的招数啊
"That'll be a neat trick...
等你死了再说"
when you're dead!"
罗斯 你不必用喊的
Ross, you don't have to yell.
刚才有爆炸 我的听力会受损
There was just an explosion, okay? My hearing would be impaired.
我觉得你很棒
I thought you were excellent.
刚才我甚至觉得"罗斯呢？"
In fact, for a minute there, I was like, "Ooh, where did Ross go?"
谢谢 你和麦克见面的第一场戏...
Thank you. And I have to say that first scene where you meet Mac...
- 怎样？ - 我的天哪
- Yeah.     - Oh, my God. I mean...
你知道吗？
You know what?
今天就到此为止 多谢帮忙
I think that's enough for today. Thanks for your help.
- 他欺压新人   - 就是啊
- Holding us back.     - Totally.